[
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "6266bc80b0e62e469cf43e98",
    "correctAnswer": "Brass",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Percussion",
      "Stringed",
      "Woodwind"
    ],
    "question": "What type of instrument is a tuba?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950bdd",
    "correctAnswer": "Scorpions",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rammstein",
      "Sodom",
      "U.D.O."
    ],
    "question": "Which German rock band released the song 'Rock You Like a Hurricane'?",
    "tags": [
      "germany",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "6266bc01b0e62e469cf43e88",
    "correctAnswer": "Woodwind",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stringed",
      "Percussion",
      "Brass"
    ],
    "question": "What type of instrument is a clarinet?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cfc",
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple",
      "Feeder",
      "Uriah Heep"
    ],
    "question": "Which English rock band released the studio album 'Help!'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b56",
    "correctAnswer": "Gorillaz",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magnum",
      "Spandau Ballet",
      "All Saints"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Damon Albarn'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950380",
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Dylan",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bruce Springsteen",
      "David Bowie",
      "Neil Young"
    ],
    "question": "Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Blood on the Tracks?",
    "tags": [
      "1970's",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b53",
    "correctAnswer": "Paramore",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice Cooper",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
      "The Velvet Underground"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Hayley Williams'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdc1",
    "correctAnswer": "Paranoid",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Psycho",
      "Crazy",
      "Insane"
    ],
    "question": "Name Black Sabbath's debut hit?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "rock_music",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe80",
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada",
      "Drake",
      "Madonna"
    ],
    "question": "Which American singer, songwriter, and actress released the studio album 'The Fame Monster'?",
    "tags": [
      "music_albums",
      "musicians",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cab",
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings",
      "Rudimental",
      "The Alan Parsons Project"
    ],
    "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Comfortably Numb'?",
    "tags": [
      "rock_music",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  }
]